https://online-msds.com/privacy-policy

Schedule a demo
Welcome to www.kha.com, the website and online service of Kelleher, Helmrich & Associates, Inc. (“KHA”). KHA is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to our website and online service, (together the “Service”). This Privacy Policy applies only to the practices of companies we own, control, or are united with under common control. By accessing or using our Service, you signify that you have read, understood and agree to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.
All capitalized terms that are not defined herein have the meanings given them in the KHA Terms of Service Agreement.
1. Information We Collect2. Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties3. Your Choices Regarding Your Information4. Security and Storage of Information5. Persons Under the Age of 136. Links to Third-party Websites7. Updates to this Privacy Policy8. Contacting Us9. Last Revision Date
1. INFORMATION WE COLLECTWe collect personal information from our users in order to provide you with a personalized, useful and efficient experience. We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service, as well as to communicate directly with you, such as to send you email messages. We may also send you Service-related emails or messages (e.g., account verification, order confirmations, change or updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices).
The categories of information we collect can include:
Account RegistrationYou can browse our site without providing personal information, but you must register in order to access most of the features of the Service. We ask for certain information such as your email address, first name, last name, company, and password when you create a KHA account, or if you correspond with us. We may also collect payment information in connection with a transaction on the Service and shipping information when you are ready to purchase or make an order.
Additional InformationAfter you setup your account, KHA members may also choose to provide additional information which may be shared with others on the Service, such as an SDS. We may retain any messages you send through the Service and information you post to the Service.
Use of cookies and other technology to collect informationWe automatically collect certain types of usage information when you visit our website or use our Service. We use or may use the data collected through cookies, log files, device identifiers, location data and web beacons to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) provide and monitor the effectiveness of our Service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, usage, and demographic patterns on our website and our Service; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems; and (f) otherwise to plan for and enhance our Service.
CookiesWhen you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click, how frequently you access the Service, and other actions you take on the Service), and allow us to track your usage of the Service over time. When you access or use the Service, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand your interests. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeted advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction(s) with KHA. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number. You can visit this page to opt out of AdRoll’s and their partners’ targeted advertising.Log DataWe may collect log file information from your browser or mobile device each time you access the Service. Log file information may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, information about your mobile device, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. We may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to anonymously track the online usage patterns of our Users.Web BeaconsIn addition, we may also use web beacons in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service.Third Parties and AffiliatesWe may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, such as Google Analytics, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit, your use of third party applications, and other information that assists us in analyzing and improving the Service. We may receive reports from third party analytics providers, which we may combine with the personal data we collect from you directly. We do not currently recognize or respond to browser-initiated Do Not Track signals as there is no consistent industry standard for compliance.Mobile Device DataWhen you access our Service by or through a mobile device, we may receive or collect and store a unique identification numbers associated with your device (“Device ID”), mobile carrier, device type and manufacturer, phone number, and, depending on your mobile device settings, your geographical location data, including GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device.
2. SHARING AND DISCLOSUREWe may share your personal information in the instances described below.
ConsentAny information or content that you voluntarily post to the Service or that you ask KHA to post to the Service on your behalf becomes available to other KHA subscribers.
Common ControlOther companies owned by or under common ownership as KHA, which also includes our subsidiaries (i.e., any organization we own or control) or our ultimate holding company (i.e., any organization that owns or controls us) and any subsidiaries it owns. These companies will use your personal information in the same way as we can under this Privacy Policy.
Third Party Service ProvidersThird party vendors, consultants and other service providers that perform services on our behalf or in order to carry out their work for us, which may include payment processing, content or service fulfillment, or providing analytics services.
Change of ControlOther parties in connection with any company transaction, such as a merger, sale of company assets or shares, reorganization, financing, change of control or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third party or in the event of bankruptcy or related or similar proceedings. Your information, including user names and email addresses, Content, and other user information may be among the items sold or otherwise transferred in these types of transactions.
Law and HarmThird parties as required to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoena/court order, legal process or other governmental request, (b) enforce our Terms of Service Agreement, including the investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of KHA, its users or the public as required or permitted by law and (e) detect, prevent or otherwise address criminal (including fraud), security or technical issues.
Aggregated/Anonymous DataWe may also share information with others in an aggregated and anonymous form that does not reasonably identify you directly as an individual, such as the number of a times a link was clicked (even if only clicked once).
3. YOUR CHOICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATIONAccount DataYou can edit and change your profile and account data through the “Settings” feature of your account.
Marketing CommunicationsIf you do not wish to receive promotional emails, you can click the “unsubscribe” button on promotional email communications. Note that you are not permitted to unsubscribe or opt-out of non-promotional messages regarding your account, such as account verification, password requests, order confirmations, change or updates to features of the Service, or technical and security notices.
Data RetentionWe will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you the Service. If your account becomes inactive, we will maintain your personal information in the event you wish to re-engage our Service. If you would like to delete your account, please contact us at support@kha.com. Once your account is deleted, the SDS associated with your account may remain available on the Service, but will no longer be associated with your use thereof.
4. SECURITY AND STORAGE OF INFORMATIONKHA cares about the security of your information and uses commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information we collect and that we share with our service providers. However, no security system is impenetrable and we cannot guarantee the security of our systems 100%. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.
Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which KHA or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which KHA or its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.
5. PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF 13Our Service is not directed to persons under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at: support@kha.com. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.
6. LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY WEBSITESThe Service may contain links to and from third party websites of our business partners, advertisers, and social media sites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies. Please check the individual policies before you submit any information to those websites.
7. UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy, we will change the “Last Revision” date below, attempt to notify you of the revised Privacy Policy via email to the email address associated with your account, and post a prominent notice on the Service for the 30 days prior to the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy. The most current version of this Privacy Policy will always be available at www.kha.com/privacy-policy
8. CONTACTING USIf you have questions about this Policy, please email support@kha.com, or write to us at: Kelleher, Helmrich & Associates, Inc. 6920 Hohman Avenue, Hammond, Indiana 46324.
9. VERSIONThis Privacy Policy was last revised on, and effective as of, May 22, 2015.
Copyright © 1985-2020Kelleher, Helmrich and Associates, Inc. All rights reserved.
